Thank you for watching!
Next, we will guide you to the car.
Good morning.
It's morning.
We are heading to Shin-Osaka for the
Kansai Collection.
It's 7 o'clock in the morning in China.
Today's...
7 and a half.
I will introduce the members next to me
today.
I was 1 out of 4.
I'm out.
By the way, the other side of the road
is...
Yoshida-yamanaka
Yamanaka-Yoshida
Oh, I can see it
So, today,
I'm going to Kyocera Dome
It's my first time to come to Kyocera
Dome
I'm going to perform there
I'm not sure if I should say this, but
this is the first step towards the dome
tour.
It's a festival, but I'm looking forward
to seeing what it's like.
We're going to the rehearsal.
We're going to the first dome in a way.
Where's the leader?
He's hiding here.
He's a shy boy.
He's a super shy boy.
I'd like to show you the first dome.
I'm nervous.
Ready, go!
It's a good start.
那厘茶。
Good morning!
We are BM. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
How is it?
It's big but I thought it's not
impossible.
Did you see me doing one-man here?
So,
we have a big idiot here.
It's been a while since we did a prank.
He's here.
How have you been, Kaito?
I'm going to a private house.
Really?
I'm shooting a video.
I'm going to shoot a video and
get a lot of views.
With the power of a celebrity.
He's nervous.
He's so nervous.
I'm the only one who's nervous.
I was scared of the prank.
I see.
I was nervous.
I'm going to disappear if you say too
much.
You're kidding.
I'm sorry.
You brought a big success.
I'm not scared.
That's it for today.
Thank you.
That was a new type of game...
Ending
Let's put it in the thumbnail
The eigternment of fighting
We are from Bknights
Fighting
Wei Joe
You can't do it.
Thank you.
Yeah!
He's trying hard.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best as a host.
You're saying that as a host.
I won't be a host for long.
I can't talk for long.
I'll watch the audience's reaction.
I'll do my best not to lose.
I think you should be confident.
We are going to stand on our own after 3
years.
We have 3 songs today.
We are practicing for the tour.
We want to show our fans that we are
still alive.
We want them to think that we are done
with the tour.
Let's do our best.
I heard that a lot of fans of Milk came
today.
They will be here for only 15 minutes.
My mom came here today.
We will shake hands.
It's not a wave.
We will do something.
We might say something.
We will communicate with fans.
We will make this a space that is not a
wave.
We will enjoy it.
We will not make eye contact.
We will do our best.
Let's do it.
The seat is high.
It's far away.
It's too far.
It's not now.
Let's do it.
Hello, we are MIRAI.
Hello.
Now
It's just before the show.
In the dressing room.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm coming to see you!
What's with the voice?
You're coming too, right?
I'm coming too!
I didn't say it, but he's coming too!
So I'm coming to see you!
I'm coming to see you!
I'm going to go!
It's the first time we're going to a
dome for the five of us.
Yeah.
We're going.
We're going to a dome where we can fill
up our military base in three years.
We're going to the dome.
Are you okay?
Calm down.
Thank you very much.
We are Nieru-kun.
Please enjoy the rest of the show.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
We're here! We've been practicing!
We're back in Tokyo!
We're back!
We were in the middle of Nil's summer
tour!
It was fun!
The next song is going to be Mezamashi!
You're going to film it!
Ready?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8!
Oh!
Oh, but it's not a foul!
You're back!
What the hell?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8!
Oh!
Dai-chan, please turn Mezamashi!
Dai-chan is in charge of Mezamashi's
close-up video!
Well, then, bye!
We'll do our best!
Take a lot of pictures!
Thank you!
Tokyo Dome in Matsumoto area
What is this?
Oh!
Let's take a bath
You!
Shut up!
There's no water left
How was the live?
You!
You're in charge of the video, right?
You lost the last time
We lost the last time
We're going to do it again today
I'm going to break my teeth
You just got a new teeth
I'm going to break your teeth and calm
down
You're lying
I forgot how to take a video
What?
What is the point of today's video?
The point of today's video is
It's raining
It's a little cloudy today
It's sad
Why?
It's been 4 years since we've been on
the show
We haven't been on the show for 5 years
We wanted to be on the show in the
spring
Rain is not sad
Rain is fun
Some people may not like rain
It may be a little cloudy
But don't worry about it
That's the good thing about the festival
We're not sad
We're not motivated
We're not stopping there
But we want to do our best
We want to do our best
What do you think, Shunta?
I don't like rain
I'm going to do the rehearsal
Please do the rehearsal
Can you do the rehearsal?
I'll do it
I have to do it
Bye
Are you okay?
It's raining
Be careful
How is it?
I'm excited
Do you want to go there?
No
Sorry
It's raining
It's better to go the other way
We're going to go there
The members were so cool and funny.
Everyone looked great, too.
Thank you for watching!
Imi and Keito
Syoo crazy
Hahahahaha
Don't be stupid
You're not supposed to talk about it.
Why?
I don't need a water gun.
You're weaker than a water gun.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors?
I'll go with Jin.
I'm going.
I'll pretend I didn't see it.
I'm not going.
Just you and me.
I don't want to.
I'm wearing good shoes today.
You go.
Why me?
I'll give you the first one.
Rock-paper-scissors.
All right!
See you, Shun.
Bye-bye.
You're not supposed to talk about it.
No, I'm not.
Come on.
All right!
Hayato.
You did it.
What are you doing?
That's all?
I'm just enjoying it.
There are many people in the back.
So, we'll do a call and response.
We can do the MC.
We'll enjoy communication.
Let's enjoy it.
Thank you.
J-BILL, BAMBAM.
BAMBAM, BAMBAM.
Why is only Yoshizaku here?
Simon.
Simon and El Paso.
They are the ones who are going to
perform.
So, please wait a little longer.
We'll start now.
The audience is cheering for the band
voclights win
Thank you
So my turn is over
But you don't think we filmed it, right?
We did it during the rehearsal
Yeah, we did it during the rehearsal
But I think we filmed a pretty rare
video
Seriously, from my point of view
The members
He didn't do it at all
Everyone, before getting in the car
We have to play rock, paper, scissors
So for the next 3 days
The members who didn't film it
Who will play it?
So, first, tomorrow's rock, paper,
scissors
Tomorrow's rock, paper, scissors
We win
No, we win
Rock, paper, scissors
So, we'll play it tomorrow
Let's get in the car
So, the day after tomorrow
Let's do it the day after tomorrow
So, day 1
So, let's do it in 2
Ok
Day 2
Ok, let's go
Let's go
Don't win
Rock, paper, scissors
Stop
Let's go
I can't get angry today.
It's early in the morning.
I was surprised.
I'm not going to give you a kiss.
Let's do our best.
Thank you.
Good morning.
It's the first day of the training camp.
How are you preparing?
I'm completely sleepy.
Good luck.
It's an easy training.
It's hot.
I'm wearing a jacket.
Let's go.
Two luxurious sugar butter,
and...
Do you want ice cream?
Cafe au lait?
One cafe au lait.
It's a cafe with a lot of glitters.
Is everyone in the frame?
Are you in the frame?
You're not in the frame, right?
I did it! I did it!
I'm the first one, right?
Yes.
I did it!
Thank you.
Wow, it's milk!
It's milk! Thank you.
I got milk and gin and ume.
Thank you.
It's the best!
I bought ice cream.
Hey, you!
It's ice cream, isn't it?
It's ice cream, isn't it? I'm supposed
to drink it.
Thank you.
Shun-chan doesn't say anything.
If you don't go early, the number of
people will be decided.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to let Koki say that I finally
met today.
I'm wondering when I'll let you say it.
Are you two close?
No, I'm not.
It's really not good.
I'm probably the only one in Ebita who
went shopping together.
I've never met him before.
It's the first time.
Jinto looks like a member.
I'm like a member.
Jinto is a deathmatch.
And this is a collaboration.
What are you talking about?
What did you know?
Jinto is too involved in the outside
world.
I'm annoyed in the Super Dragon.
I'm not.
I'm being teased.
I see.
I'm going to take a commemorative photo.
There are so many people.
Good morning.
It's the same as always.
What is this?
What was this?
Milk camera.
It's a summary of the summer event.
I see.
I'm going to make a devil.
Yes.
Milk, banana.
I got it.
Good bye.
Good morning.
Today is the first day of the event.
How are you?
I'm fine.
It's early in the morning.
It's too early.
Your mother is coming to see you.
My mother doesn't come to see me.
I've been coming to see the shrimp.
Did you come here the day before
yesterday?
Yes.
I went to the sea in Wakayama.
I'm a fisherman.
I'm going to the sea with my family.
I'm already planning to go on a trip.
I was surprised to see the shrimp.
I'm going to appear more than usual this
time.
My mother won't come.
I'll do my best in the video later.
Let's do our best.
I'm going to the sea.
出つけた 登る 一瞬 素敵でもな
飌ふ 그림 永 steroid toma fu
Blood blood blood blood, blood blood
Let's try it with a mouth open.
Ready, go!
Good morning.
It's cold.
Did you sleep well last night?
I was in a bad mood.
What is this camera?
This is Milk You Choose.
It was a mischievous.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Please give us a high rating.
With ta habit of singing along…
Let's run!
In the moving story
With a feeling
To give boild six generations
I want to drive to protect it
Hearing the sound of the stage and the
bass,
the tension around dancing has just
rockets high.
The performance is the highlight.
HiMix K着品
We are going to perform on the stage.
Thank you very much.